[
  {
    "question": "Who Owns A Beet Farm?",
    "possbileAnswers": ["Dwight", "Toby", "Erin"],
    "correctAnswer": "Dwight"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is Jim's Last Name?",
    "possbileAnswers": ["Schrute", "Mcquire", "Halpert"],
    "correctAnswer": "Halpert"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who Did Michael Get Married To?",
    "possbileAnswers": ["Holly Flax", "Jan Levinson", "Carol Stills"],
    "correctAnswer": "Holly Flax"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is The Name Of The Company They Work At",
    "possbileAnswers": [
      "Scranton Paper Company",
      "Dunder Scott Paper Company",
      "Dunder Mifflin Paper Company"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Dunder Mifflin Paper Company"
  },
  {
    "question": "What City Does The Show Take Place In?",
    "possbileAnswers": ["Philidephia", "Scranton", "Chicago"],
    "correctAnswer": "Scranton"
  },
  {
    "question": "What State Is That In?",
    "possbileAnswers": ["Indiana", "Pennslyvania", "Iowa"],
    "correctAnswer": "Pennslyvania"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Many Seasons Of The Show Where There?",
    "possbileAnswers": ["7", "8", "9"],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where Does Michael Take Everyone For His Birthday?",
    "possbileAnswers": ["Ice Skating", "Bowling", "The Zoo"],
    "correctAnswer": "Ice Skating"
  },
  {
    "question": "Near What Tourist Attraction do Jim and Pam get Married?",
    "possbileAnswers": [
      "Statue Of Liberty",
      "Niagra Falls",
      "Empire State Building"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Niagra Falls"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Job Does Stanley Do?",
    "possbileAnswers": ["Sales", "Human Resources", "Accounting"],
    "correctAnswer": "Accounting"
  }
]
